[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Залишитись (на ночівлю)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Тренування' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "れんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Прання' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せんたく"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Прибирання' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そうじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Починається' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はじまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Новий тип, стиль' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんがた"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відчиняти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひらきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зал, приміщення' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Насолоджуватися, розважатися' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たのしみます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Проспект, головна дорога' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おおどおり"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вищезазначене, понад, більше' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Статуя' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぞう"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стрибки на конях' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けいば"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Динозавр' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "きょうりゅう"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'Будівля' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たてもの"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'Знімати(відео), робити(фото), робити репродукцію' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うつします"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відображення, картинка, кліп,фото' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "えいぞう"
    }
]